And with that, and with that, we've reached the last few minutes of this program.
You remember we started out in week one, vibe coding for Fun and Profit.
We built out, we went through all of the IDEs, just introducing like agents
that MD, cursor, co-pilot, codecs,
anti-gravity, looking at all those plugins and the IDEs themselves.
Then our first experience with YOLO, it feels like an age away.
And then the commercial MVP that was cool.
Then we moved into claw code and open code and AMP.
It was commands and checkpoints
for the first time, the slash commands and Ralph loops.
And then we, things got more serious.
We got to see that whole workflow with Jira
that was cool all the way going through to a git push
and built out that legal SAS platform.
And that finally took us to week three.
By this point I said that you were now vibe engineering.
You've gone from vibe coding to vibe engineering
as a professional.
And now this week was so much fun.
I knew it would be.
We just went crazy with first of all
the idea of multi-agents, which is kind of worrying.
But then sub-agents, I showed you hooks.
Sandboxing was a much more interesting day
than it might have sounded just from the name,
Sandboxing, when we were doing,
I think that for me, anyway,
Sprite.dev is the really, really great thing,
but also running with Cloud Code remotely,
hopefully you tried the Ampersand thing
and also using it from your mobile
and then also tagging Cloud in a Git issue.
It's fantastic.
Then the large co-base workflow day,
I didn't really do much about what large co-base workflow
'cause I felt like we covered it enough.
But yeah, instead we spent a moment
looking at some of the other stuff.
I got it, I think that the Claude Agent SDK
is really interesting.
Something that's definitely worth more exploration
if you found that, that's something useful. And then of course we looked
at co-work and an open claw was just something to take a nod at. It's all over the news, at least
for me at the moment. And then the last couple of days have just been so great looking at orchestrators,
of course, GSD, Claude agent teams, which is definitely my favourite. And then also the craziness that is gas town which was something we
did today and then we finally very quickly I showed you Codex subagents and
then getting Codex to fix up the massive API so we could have a real finance
workstation hopefully you've recreated that yourself that completed our capstone
project project number four.
But I know what you're thinking.
We didn't do four projects.
We did six projects because we also did the first person shooter on the first day,
and we did the space invaders.
So if they count as projects, so that would make it six projects.
Four commercial projects though.
And that means of course that you are no longer a vibe coder, you are no longer a vibe engineer, you are now and officially an
agentic engineer, I can fell in that third strip, you have completed the board,
it's done, you're an agentic engineer, congratulations. And it remains me to
give you a huge thank you, thank you so much for surviving the rollercoaster,
making it all the way to the end.
I promised you a roller coaster and I think I delivered.
So remember, whether you like it or not,
something came with this package
that is yours that you can't avoid.
It's like a mandatory part of it.
And that is me.
I come with it.
You get me forever.
I want you to reach out to me post on LinkedIn
that you've completed the course
with something you've learned, some insight,
something about it and I will come in
and amplify your success,
make sure that others know about it.
I'd love it if you post some of the projects you've built
or some of your thoughts on what you like and dislike
about the different platforms you've covered
or the techniques.
As I say, post the certificate,
that's something that is easy for me to amplify.
I would love to do so.
Take a look through some of my other courses.
If that interests you, I've got lots of stuff to build you into being an AI engineer and
have a program for people who want to become proficient AI engineers.
I should also mention, my editor would kill me, I didn't mention again, that to the extent
you're willing to rate this course, that is the
main way that Udemy decides whether or not to recommend it to others. So if
you found it useful then please do rate it. It makes an enormous difference
and I'm super grateful. But more important than any of this, the single
most important thing for you, the to-do that you must do, is to build. It's all
about building. I hope that I have equipped you with the missing manual to this this alien tool that
André Capati spoke of.
You now have the ability to use this tool.
Go use it.
Go build some amazing things.
Build them.
Share them with me.
I can't wait to see them.
Thank you so much again.